A Guide to the Minutes of the Virginia Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Board, 1979-2004
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Minutes of the Virginia Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Board, 1979-2004
The Library of Virginia
50382
3.35 cu. ft. (4 boxes)
Virginia Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Board
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 23 April 2012 from the Virginia Dept. of Bureau and Labor, Richmond, VA.
Biographical Information
The Virginia Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Commission was created by an act of the General Assembly in 1978. In 1985 the name of the Commission was changed to the Virginia Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Board and in 1987 the Board was placed administratively under the Virginia Dept. of Labor and Industry. In 2004 the Board moved under the Virginia Employment Commission.
The Board serves as an advisory body to the Governor and General Assembly on matters relating to the migrant and seasonal farmworker (MSFW) population in Virginia and provides a forum for the sharing of information and concerns. The Board, comprised of 15 members appointed by the Governor and approved by the General Assembly, includes representatives from the grower community, migrant and seasonal farmworkers, the general public, and public and private agencies. The Board provides coordination and evaluation of state and federal services and, to the degree feasible, other governmental, public and private agency services to migrant and seasonal farmworkers within the Commonwealth; identifies and evaluates of the needs of migrant and seasonal farmworkers, as well as the needs of their employers; identifies of the problems of the target population, provides background information, and recommends options for solutions; encourages and fosters of the development of area migrant and seasonal farmworker councils to seek problem resolution and communication at the local level.
Scope and Content
Minutes and related attachments, 1979-2004, documenting the activities and decisions of the Virginia Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Board. Also includes correspondence, reports, annual reports, and committee meeting notes.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Minutes, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1987 January-May (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minutes, 1987 July-December (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Minutes, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Minutes, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Minutes, 1990 March-August (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Minutes, 1990 October-December (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Minutes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Minutes, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Minutes, 1994 March-November (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Minutes, 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Minutes, 1995 January-June (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Minutes, 1995 June-July (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Minutes, 1995 September-October (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Minutes, 1995 November-December (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Minutes, 1996 January (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Minutes, 1996 January-March (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Minutes, 1996 March-April (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Minutes, 1996 May-June (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Minutes, 1996 July-November (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Minutes, 1996 December (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Minutes, 1997 January-March (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 1997 March-June (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 1997 June-September (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 1997 September-December (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 1998 January-March (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1998 April-October (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Minutes, 1998 October-December (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Minutes, 1999 January-April (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Minutes, 1999 April-June (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Minutes, 1999 June-August (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Minutes, 1999 August-September (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Minutes, 1999 September-December (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Minutes, Annual reports, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Minutes, 2000 January-April (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Minutes, 2000 April (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Minutes, 2000 April-July (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Minutes, 2000 July-August (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Minutes, 2000 September-October (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Minutes, 2000 October-December (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Minutes, 2001 January-February (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 2001 March-May (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 2001 May-July (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Minutes, 2001 July (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Minutes, 2001 July-September (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 2001 October (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
- Minutes, 2001 October-December (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Minutes, Annual reports, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Minutes, 2002 January (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
- Minutes, 2002 January-April (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Minutes, 2002 April (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
- Minutes, 2002 April-August (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Minutes, 2002 August-October (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Minutes, 2002 October-December (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Minutes, 2003 January-April (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Minutes, 2003 April-June (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Minutes, 2003 July-August (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Minutes, 2003 August-October (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Minutes, 2003 November-December (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Minutes, 2004 January-February (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 2004 March-April (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Minutes, 2004 April-July (Box 4, Folder 3)